cdnsun.com 2019-03-12

# Privacy Policy | CDNsun

## Privacy Policy

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you visit our website, log in or sign in, place an order or fill out a form on our website. 

  * We collect information contractually necessary to provide our service, provide support and execute purchases. This information includes full name, email address, company name, company address, phone number (see also 2FA), company VAT number and company registration number. You can manage this information on the Billing/Settings page and via our support helpdesk. 
  * We collect cookies. Cookies are small files that our website transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you decide to allow cookies in your browser's settings) that enable our website to recognize your browser and remember certain information such as that you are logged in. We also use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of our advertisements and compile aggregate data about website traffic and website interactions so that we can offer better website experience. Cookies are stored for a limited period of time. By allowing cookies in your browser and visiting our website you understand, agree and accept that we use and collect cookies. 
  * We collect logs. We collect logs from our website containing data such as your IP address, type of your browser (User Agent), HTTP Referer, etc. for debugging purposes and also because in certain cases (such as payments) we are legally required to do so. Logs are stored for a limited period of time. 

### What do we use your information for?

The information we collect from you may be used in the following ways.

  * To provide our service and support and execute purchases. 
  * To improve our service, support and website and to personalize your experience. We continually improve our service, support and website based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 
  * To send automated and periodic emails. The email address you provide us, is used to send you information about your services, balance, orders, payments and other activities on our website. And in addition to send you occasional (one or two emails per quarter) company news, updates and related product or service information. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe (opt-out) from receiving company news, updates and related product or service information emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. It is recommended to be subscribed to receiving company news, updates and related product or service information emails as they may contain important information such as updates of our Terms and Conditions, our pricing, our infrastructure, etc., if you are unsubscribed from receiving these emails then it is your responsibility to review our website periodically to familiarize yourself with any modifications. If you want to check or modify (such as re-subscribe) your subscription to receiving company news, updates and related product or service information emails please contact our support. 

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal data. We implement Two Factor Authentication. We limit your personal data only to what is strictly necessary. We store your personal data only for a limited period of time. All supplied sensitive payment information such as credit card number is only transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to our payment gateway providers and it is not stored on our servers. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personal data to outside parties for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than trusted third-parties, our business partners, who assist us in operating our service and website. These third-parties are limited to only accessing personal data necessary to provide their services to us and must provide reasonable assurances that they will appropriately safeguard the personal data. We may share your personal data with our affiliates. We may also release your personal data when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our website policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We value your privacy and thus we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personal data to outside parties for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than trusted third-parties, our business partners, who assist us in operating our service and website. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our website may make any changes to their personal data at anytime by logging into client section and going to the Billing/Settings page. 

### General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

We value your privacy and thus we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). For more details please visit our GDPR page which is included under the scope of this Privacy Policy. 

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website and services.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This agreement was last modified on May 30, 2018.

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy from time to time without notice. You understand, agree and accept that it is your responsibility to review our Privacy Policy periodically to familiarize yourself with any modifications. 

You understand, agree and accept that continued use of this site after such modifications for more than 1 month will constitute acknowledgment and agreement of the modified Privacy Policy. You understand, agree and accept that if we don't receive a notice of disagreement from you within 1 month since the Privacy Policy modification, you will be deemed to have accepted the modified Privacy Policy. 

### Contact Information

If there are any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below.

  * Office: V zářezu 902/4, Prague, 158 00, Czech Republic
  * Website: [cdnsun.com](https://cdnsun.com/)
  * Email: info@cdnsun.com
  * Phone: +420 776 256 872

## What next?

Read about the following topics.

  * Terms & Conditions
  * General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
